ASHWINI SAWANT

Contact

Ç.

8655367527

sawant.ashwini4@gmail.com

48/1091, kannamwar Nagar - 1 vikhroli (East) Mumbai Maharashtra 400083 INDIA

Personal Statement

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, currently looking to resume my professional career after dedicating the 3.5 years of experience in the field of accounting & auditing service as an article clerk & 4.5 years of experience in the field of taxation.

I am confident that I can help to build reputation of organization. I believe the knowledge and skills built up during this time make me the perfect candidate for the role.

Work Experience

MACLEODS PHARMACEUTICALS LTD, ANDHERI SR. OFFICER TAXATION

Full Time

Dec 2011 - Present

- 1. Responsible for monitoring tax flow on monthly basis & timely TDS payment of Tax deducted on salary, suppliers payment, scrap etc.
- 2. preparation quarterly TDS returns,

manage tax provision and tax compliance process.

3. Generating Form 16 & Form 16A.

SUSHIL & CO., MARINE LINES ARTICLE CLERK

Full Time

Apr 2009 - Oct 2011

- 1. Responsible for TDS data entry, TDS Returns filling.
- 2. Preparation of profession Tax Returns.
- 3. Responsible for accounting of entity, balance sheet, cash & fund floe statement.
- 3. Handling matters of Income Tax with ITO for refund.
- 4. Income Tax Return filing for Individual & company.

SANJAY RANE & ASSOCIATES, WADALA ARTICLE CLERK

Full Time

Jul 2007 - Mar 2009

- 1. Responsible for Tax Audit of firms & professionals.
- 2. Handling concurrent audit of various scheduled banks & Risk based audit of Dena Bank (BKC).
- 3. Preparation of Audit report.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI

MUMBAI 2009-2009

Degree BCOM

Maharashtra state board

Mumbai 2006-2006

High School Qualification

HSC (First Class)

Maharashtra state board

Mumbai 2004-2004

High School Qualification

SSC (First Class)

Key Skills

- Ability to Learn New Skills Quickly
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Communication Skills
- Loyalty
- Working to Deadlines

Languages

Marathi

Fluent

Hindi

Fluent

English

Advanced

Certifications

▶ 100 HRS computer Training with ICAI

Activities and Interests

READING & MUSIC